Hello Hello Album Printing of a Metro Channel
Friends, in today's video
we also discussed market trends by
testing all the important indicators and as
I saw in all the indicators and updates in this video,
right now the market is
consolidating with a correction of a small level,
a bullish momentum is going on,
some indicators are giving their important
technical support, after this the
person is again reporting on some of his long-term train
track decisions by making a challenge space on it and doing
research on the bar from there, so
this wallet may remain intact for a few days,
so we feel that this is the
time to keep a check on some things and take a little care,
severe pain investment, staggered admission,
while if you get the opportunity, keep replying, keeping
all these news and indicators in mind,
which fundamentally
songs can be considered for entry from top to top investment,
which ones you can
repair at good valuation, which
festivals can you click on, we will
discuss that in this video friends, if
you have subscribed to my channel  If you haven't done it, do it
now and press back
because I keep updating it on a weekly basis
and keep sharing with you my voice of the best of two sisters, which can be
very useful for you, so without
taking any more fear time, let's get
started friends, as I have been doing one by one in the last two days,
in today's video also
we are going to share so many staff officers
that I will not be able to give you the details of all the staff,
this video will become very long,
but those who are regular members of our channel,
Mohit, will be very well aware of all the staff
because
we have definitely done the detailed review of all the staff
in some video in different pack channel lists on the channel,
friends, this video is
Williams rate today price, but I will also give a quick introduction
of all the staff for our new viewers so
that you can get an idea of ​​what all the companies use
and why all these stock fundamentals are
for long term investment,
then I can do typing set light jump right into words, so
friends, today's
first companies of depression, Bajaj Finance is a very
Strong and such a very good welcome non-
banking finance corporation after 50 minutes
it opposes Bajaj group
and it is a very good well managed company its
corporate governance is good it is also a
very smart company because several
factors that they have discussed in a different
support video the team had talked about stocks of banking and insurance
sector so in this we
talked about market performance in some detail
and soon I will bring a fundamentals
mein aashiqui video on this we will
talk in more detail why Bajaj has such a mooted
business clear in this sector so
now what to do if you find a point player it seems like a
good spot but if it is a long term
investment then first press this
top level you can keep it that is between 4547 to 4547 favorite level
second
price level if there is such a big fall difficult
job sentiments then the
level of 3537 can also give very attractive price
travel portal long term investment in
Bajaj Finance friends next company is housing
finance companies
You can also name some relatively small companies and actresses,
but one fundamental force
from when small companies are low on market
assessment is that they have a
very strong written letter and business
management.
I think this could be a very
good investment option for the future. Based on
awards and performances,
we operate in Rajasthan.
In North India, a small finance bank had a
housing loan subsidy called Palace. This
new housing finance company is now called
Awaaz Ventures. Financial Officer Shoot
Companies: Currently, these people have
revealed market assessment and
cater more to semi-urban and rural areas.
I like two or three companies. The biggest
company is HDFC Development Finance
Corporation. We are going to
talk about it later in the video. It
seems to me to be a topic because it has a very good
spread in India, its name is very good, its application is
very good, business management is very
good. But along with this, if you
want to pet any sports player and
want to see the market and want to tap its growth potential,
then Awaaz Senses can be quite  Often, if the
price is not the first price to regulate the fall on Thors, then I
think it can be tight, that is 2050-2150,
if you want to wait a little and this
also includes some midcap, smallcap and midcap
companies, small companies, so there is some pressure in this,
then if
365 is tied then the price of 1750-1850 will become
quite attractive, you can take
its second test meeting, which is
around 2018, so you can wait for that price trend
if you want to wait a little in it,
but I think if
you get this first presenter, now it is a
little above this price range, a little and
if there is a fall of two to three percent and it
comes in this price range, then definitely you can look at this
point waiting for long
term, the next company with problem market
share in the paint industry
is Asian Paints, the company with problem market share is of more than
fifty percent domestic, that is,
decorative friends, if we talk about
Differently from
Asian Paints, neither Mandal nor Mandal are very
strong companies. They are quite old but have a
strong degree.
Asian Paints is the first price to update it. It
could be 24 or 25 percent. If it
falls a little further, it
falls by two to three percent. Currently, its
price range is around 22%. If there is a slight decline, then
it is
definitely looking at a single platform from a
long-term perspective. If you
want to wait for a little more decline, then for 22%
you can see that the last time there was a
decline, the last round there was a decline. It was
around 2275 and its second day's
low is around 2275. We will definitely add that
you can locate for
long term investment in Asian Paints
from our company naukri.com, which you know is a
scam. We are talking about this company. It is also a
fundamentally strong company, like many
businesses perform well, especially  I
definitely know with naukri.com, I
pin it and it is also in a round bottle, then there were many
staff members who were in the metro, so
you can see the fundamentals of Infosys's job,
from this picture he is the
director, he is also a very rapid investor, the
staff reporter, he has
good stakes in many businesses, so if you
want to activate these for schools, then none can be the
most important skill, if you
see this method of long term growth, then
politician and a gifted, quite cleverly
good price, years chapter
support, only that, where you
can add in the departure, but if you
should wait a little, as you have seen, there is a lot of
momentum in this,
as you can also see crime, so if you
want to wait a little, then you
can update the traffic near 3536, if it
comes to this before this year, then definitely
attempted support levels for long term
investment in which naukri.com next
company is a Digvijay Singh ji company,
monopoly in India
Nestle India, the market leader in its sector, is a
Switzerland based best company, it is a
multinational company, we are talking about its Indian celebs
in India, to do this back
minute you can see that the sum
is the moving average on this, the range is around
16000 to 16000 and a half, the flavor is
very attractive and here you
can definitely set your accommodation,
if you want to wait a little, a little more
conservative approach, then you can fit the level of 15000 to 15000 and a half,
there also
special mention can be started in a very aggressive channel,
friends, next company,
next step, my favorite staff, bank,
university, such things, India's
largest private sector for all over India,
strong bank for Muzaffarnagar and
HDFC Bank, HDFC Bank, etc.
I feel that setting on to can with regard to 1415,
if you have not done your positive juice, then
definitely dandruff facility can watch out for,
but  You might want to wait a little
if you think that when its length
starts getting declared, there might be
some correction in the bank, there might be some pressure in the factor,
like it
can diesel all the points, there might be some problem while declaring master kids, so
if you want to wait a little then you
can wait for the level of 1213,
there definitely add thank you, very very strong
contender for long term
investment, the next step is also one of my
favorite banks and Kotak does not go,
HDFC Bank officials have fundamentalism, it is a
small bank,
and the number of networks because if we talk about the
number of branches and the loan
book, then it is a very small bank in such a matter,
but still it is a fundamentally very
strong bank, its DSP is quite
good, so I think long-term
interest is important, it is a
bank, if you
want to enroll Kotak Mahindra Bank, then you can tweet them from April 17-18,
this proposal is still going on
that I
can start my department department here first  You can
see support many times on this planet. There is
support at two, three, or four places, so this can
definitely bring a good starting
point for long-term investment.
But if you want to wait a little, you
can update the sign-in 1415 till there. If there is a
correction because after B.Com
semester, this bank and fundamentally there is
no vision of such a big correction.
But if the overall investment
becomes tasty, how does the banking sector get preserved in the B sector?
If you see any such friends, then
definitely they can be
responsible for the development of long-term
interest. Mill capital, these are technical. The
next company we can focus on,
friends, is Titan Company. If we talk about
its business, it is a key business,
but its most important business, from which
its maximum profit does not
come, but more than 80 percent revenue comes. They
want to pocket 20%. There seems to be a
possibility of removing its jewellery prices from a small amount
because of the excise duty on it.  It
seems that the season will be a little
Chinese, so because of all these things, there were a
few 65 murders in the title, so 3000
goodbye, whenever there is any pressure
from a student due to current tax, 2002
good time to find all cities in great
start for long term, so after a
minute of typing, the first question came out which I think could be
good, the
second price range of 1350 1450, if you want to wait for it, then it is
1213, which you can wait for,
you can see there and its movie
episode is running around 1323 50, so
definitely type keyboard price check, look
into consideration for long term, next
companies part of multinational company Bata
India, let's talk about the
gift Prem business of Bata, its Indian subsidiary, it is the
market leader, very good search, along with
Relax, another company
I like is Pathak Significant
President Kunwar, when the market was hit, it
also got hit very badly, there will be a huge
decline.  And there has
n't been much recovery from there yet, you
can see that it is also around its March Twenty20
levels. You can see that the
March
Quid is around the same level in March, which is
its level today,
rather around that, there hasn't been much recovery yet,
and this has happened because
you know that the footwear sector of Bate
comes, this tweet comes, along with that, there is
also the shift of their children going to school,
so all those shops have
not opened properly yet, the ones that were open themselves have
also started closing again, so due to all those
factors, this is causing problems in Bate India,
but after deleting it from its enemies, it
again
declined, it has been going on for the entire 13 to 14 years,
rather it is going on in the middle, almost around now, if
you see it anywhere around To Be Responsible, then
this distemper is good cause notice to
protect meeting Bate India in physics,
if you make a statement, then the first press love can be
13 and a half to 14 why, there are
many of its moving averages here  But you
can see that the to-do group sent you
can get around 1450 and it is moving below that, so
many such song tops do not stay below the
morning habit of Women's Day for very long.
However, since Bata
India is also a little susceptible because when
tweeting soldiers awaken
sentiments, then if I want to activate you on gas pricing, then if this is
not
possible to extend Milton Water, but if you
want to wait a little, then they can add 12.5 to 13
rupees anytime. If there is a
little more decline, there is a little more beating in
butter, then you can start doing extensive research on that decision.
But this is a
very strong company, G Road Company, a
good initiative, comment company, I will also
do motor in my sector, so
I see good growth
potential of all these things in Pavata in this network for the long term.
So, in this dynasty update, Wicketkeeper
Nylon Audio, long term investment, the next
companies are pharmaceutical companies, but only
pharmaceutical companies in this, between left shift +,
you can consider it as average.
PM Chief Let us talk about Procter & Gamble help,
going back, this company is
very active in the market, using the products of this company regularly,
companies with good market penetration, this top 5 minutes can
already increase, the
current price of our mustard juice is quite good, in fact, it is
quite close, a little more correction, if you
wait a little, then that paste
code will
now have a very attractive
price, you
can start your admission there, but if you
want to wait a little, then you can update the puncture from 5,000,
there it can definitely be very attractive,
brother update level, the next
company is of India,
if you talk about it, then
fundamentally, the
company is of good market, it has a
good market, fat free company is
small cap, but well mannered, its good
growth potential, in this also if you
want to play the travel industry, tourism
industry, airline industry, you
can be a player in all these, VIP industries, then
if you want to start visiting
325 350  You can update the level of , it
is very close to it, a little bit
and if correction comes in it, if it starts to grow, then
different
correction in it can become a trend, so if this
trend is between 325 to 350, then
definitely you can start looking at this
company for long term investment, if you
want to wait a little more and
want to bear the brunt of the city, small cap
companies can become a little pressure, in this, the
qualities of the company are seen between 275 to 300
trend, so definitely it can be a
good price, love to talk meeting VIP
Industries for stomach, the next company
Whirlpool's World Track International
company, UC company, its Indian subsidy,
Rudrapur, India, I am talking to you,
this is also a very good stroke player, it is a
battery company, motor business, it has a good
market, not only air conditioners but
also in washing machine shipment, refrigerator,
for watching this is a white goods sector,
companies having a good market,
Whirlpool India, to regulate Whirlpool
You
can keep an eye on the price range and keep it around its 20-20
moving average. This is personal
responsibility of course
and this current price is around 12 months. So
if you feel that by raising money, then
definitely you can start regulating
Whirlpool India for long term. But if you
want to wait a little and you feel that there may be a
little more decline in the stock, then you can
invest in the festival of 2021 and you can make
your recommendation there. Whirlpool
India is a
very strong player in white goods. Voltas and
Voltas Tata Group companies are
mostly such a focused company. If we
talk about Whirlpool, then it definitely works in a lot of white goods like
AC, refrigerator, washing machine, teacher
appointment and many other things,
but Voltas Exclusive is also
such a focused player and it is a very
fundamentals and company. Now if we talk about a lot of details of the
company and total white goods admittedly,
especially if we talk about such segment, then there are
many details, special things that are
behind it.  To benefit from Voltas tablets,
I think the first question that
can arise is its
front price range of around 950 to 950 rupees.
If you want to weigh it from another perspective, then it can be
between 950 to 850 rupees. Here also it is around 860 rupees. So
definitely that can be the
price. That is what you can debate and look
for. Fundamentally, it is a very soft company. This
kid is quite controlled. Management and business
operations are very good. Prince, all things should be factored in.
Whatever prices you find
more competitive for long term
investment, you can keep an eye on the
next companies. Snow Peak Friends is a
multinational pharmaceutical company. We are
talking about its Indian Stock Exchange.
For a minute, the first
price has been calculated in the range of 75 to 786 rupees. The
second price can be weighed in paise at
7077 rupees. It is a very good brand
in the pharmaceutical industry. Its
dividend history is also very good. It is quite good.  It does
different things, it is a good company for
long term investment,
so the fundamentals are quite
soft, there is no need to worry about companies,
if you want to
invest in fennel for different things, you should also do different things, so it lagged
behind this year,
whereas all three companies' dead plays can also be very good,
and since it is a pharmaceutical
industry, then a lot of defense staff
can be recruited, the leading company for your defense staff selection is
Abhilasha, about India,
about multinational pharmaceutical companies
based company, its Indian subsidiary is
Airport India Chairman Prabhat Kar, and
you will also
see the same similar interesting observation, this is also the
moving average black line of stock updates, it is
coming down from that profile, so
definitely ad song top does
not remain below its 2nd day's movie way for long,
so definitely I think that if this
problem seems attractive for long term
investment, and definitely this is
the price according to these girls, consultant
For long term investment,
your investment will be released. For long term
insurance, if you
want to wait a little, then you
can wait for the range of Rs 12,500 to Rs 13,500. If
you find that festival more attractive for the long term, then
if you want to update, then the
next company is not very
strong players in the retail sector of India. Abhinav
Supervisor is more known by the name of low demand. There is
no need for me to tell much about it. There is a
very strong foot in the retail sector. It is a very
good motor business, debt free business. Or
all the lines where there are Bhim shops,
which are retail chains, they
also do all the land there, so they do
not need much debt. There is good
operating growth. They
keep inventory of this treatment.
Inventory is processed very fast.
Due to this, they are able to give good discounts.
Karan's detailed customer base also keeps
increasing in good quantity. Rough test has been
given positive, although it has been
shown in profit numbers, but if the remaining revenue numbers are
clear, then they have good
quantity in it.  Although a slight recovery was seen in the stock, but its
huge number of cases is increasing,
due to which the transmission is again looking a little
in the stop, but for the long term, if you can make
it an alternative to
depression, you can fold this stock,
each unit can provide good
returns in the future. If you
want to start regulating this leaf, then you can
start admission at the price slashed price range of ₹100 at 2704 2850, you can wait for it in other crops, you can
maintain it, most of the
officer 2550, there is a little more pressure in the next stop because of any
external
number of office tops, admission on that on this occasion and
if in such an environment you can start these
innovative supermodels, the next company is typing
and related to it and we had a little more
detailed discussion about it when we discussed the best of
foreign investment in the first step, to
break the eighth quality, a little more detailed
meditation, so in such a situation, if you
see a little long competition  Very good initiative
garment company, this is also almost free company,
well garment company is very good, in
fast, in a lot of details,
fundamentals of great, then you will
see very good points, which is the
best of fundamental research problem
if you want to invest  If you want, you can fit the level of ₹15 to ₹1550, yes,
just a little around the price camp and if there is a correction in it, then
definitely it can be a very strong
candidate for long term investment,
on that decision, but if you want to wait a little, then you can
reduce petrol price by 12.50 to 13,
that too is a very good attractive
price level and its two hundred,
its moving average is also around the level of 12, so
if this stock falls to that level,
it still falls, then
definitely you can talk meeting Master
Polytechnic for long term on the next stock
Eicher Motors India, the
legendary Indian company Royal
Enfield, which makes two wheelers, the 240cc motorcycle, is not that brand, it is Eicher Motors
and only two wheelers, it makes four wheeler
commercial vehicles in collaboration
with Volvo, so their performance
and it makes commercial vehicles, it has a very
good brand record from motivational
And Royal
Enfield and many more friends, you have many
motorcycles as well as different Galaxy
series, so to invest in Eicher Motors,
I think that the
price of 24-horsepower motorcycles is the first festival which has become quite
attractive, secondly you
can keep your reserve register, one from this,
definitely backed very attractive
price, at that time lifting, till Akshar Motors, this
chocolate investment is very strong companies,
factory companies, good operation, retail
business is quite good, and friend
request, sometimes if it is motor business then it is
different, I think that the first year long
term potential in Ashram Motors J2
Price in this chapter, nylon and
you will feel more comfortable in both these wires,
from there you can start your item loans, your
investment, in these,
Ashram Motors has
Agni company related to the banking sector,
but if I talk, then the
best friends, I already have to talk about
HDFC Bank and Kotak Mahindra Bank,
both these are my favorite banks, but the
history of Axis Bank has
not been very good, but their current
management is quite good, Amitabh ji
Shankar, Managing Director, his history is
quite good. Tesla model, he had done a very good job.
So I think that in the future,
Axis Bank may cool down a bit.
Today, I will take these PHP shoes. They are using it. It may be a
little dress, it may be a
tweet also. Amber Gift Pack. If we
talk about the four private sector banks, then the
press of this private sector bank, DSC, Kotak Mahindra, Axis Arise, all these
four banks seem good. What
attracts me in all these banks is the
investment feature. One of them, Axis
Bank, has seen a good improvement
from its all time traditional. So if
you want to do a minute, you can tweet for 625, 675 rupees.
Similarly,
these earrings around it can create that impression. The
next thing we keep
talking about is another big IT company of India, TCS and Infosys.
Profile Options Point comes to IT
sector in 2000. But such technology is actually very
from player, electric small player from both of them.
TCS and Infosys are small players,
but actually, when they start making computers,
I think those who are serious about bringing them
in very soon, they are going to look at a lot of tractors,
service sectors, and different sperm
marketplaces,
and on the
basis of all those parents, we will do a holistic
comparison. Quantity Banaras will do a
lot of stroke players of certain
industries, compare them against each other,
and see who comes out as the winner. Then we will
check technologies
in the IT sector, but right now I can tell
you that technology can definitely be a very
strong player in the future.
Its fit Mandleshwar is very good. Its business
management operations are very good. Its
corporate governance has been very good. I
also refer to the comments below. So,
I think this chapter note scan will
definitely be the first price inch for admitting
TCS Infosys Technologies on PM Cares from IT player wicketkeeper channels. It is
around the current price range, but there is a possibility of a
little more decline.  If you get great, then it is
possible that you may get it at this price
and other friends can wait for it,
which can be double the important support.
Next important support level
was between 800 to all the WhatsApp, so
definitely made a very attractive price
table update. HCL Technologies for
long term SUCA has a good growth potential in this
company. The next company ABCL is a non-
banking finance company. It is the
market leader in final gold finance in India.
It has the highest number
of customer points.
Muthoot Finance seems to be a better company than Mannapuram Finance because of the
side effects. I will discuss it
in a separate video. Muthoot
Finance will be discussed in a video. But
if you talk about its price sense, then there can be a
time table of 11 to 12,
where you can cut your investment calculations.
If you wanted to wait a little, then the
price is 1000 to 11, you
can update it anytime, that too will
increase the attractive price.
Long term investment in North  The
next gas distribution company,
Mahanagar Gas,
operates our system in Muslim Mumbai and growing areas.
Fundamentally, it is a very good company.
And from various companies, I
see good growth potential for the indicator. So,
Indraprastha Gas is also a
good company. I have also talked to DSP.
I have checked current prices in earlier videos. If we
talk about price levels,
Mahanagar Gas seems to have a good price.
Its price is quite good
as I remember. So, to do this combination,
I think it is a
special thing fashionable from here.
If you want to wait a little, you
can wait for practical 900 to 1000
there. You can do it in your universe and if you
start an acid, Mahanagar is the
next company in the general insurance sector.
India's market leader in the private
sector, ICICI Lombard. It is also
fundamentally an office company. Life
insurance companies, Uber Insurance
sector, your talk to us about the importance potential.
India is a very underrated
market and its future growth
potential is quite high.  It is good Biswal All the
best
according to the company in the general insurance sector
in India ICICI Lombard so to
calculate this, the first proposal can be brought from
1314 and a half from the second rather if you
want to wait then it is the fastest festival of Bhairav ​​from anger,
this company is
India's leading housing finance company
HDFC Limited Housing Development
Finance Corporation December parent company
Ford Endeavour Group cutting side HDFC
Bank HDFC Life in chief and God
Limited of all these tent companies that problem we are
talking about here HDFC Limited has an
attractive price before 24 and 25 clothes to update but if you
want to wait a little you can see
its dowry movie which is around 2223
so this attractive price is a
browser so like this just look at the tractor price
Jabalpur attack million for long term in
HDFC Limited has
its company Edifice of Management Company
HDFC AMC Asif Management Companies have better complete
I think HDFC AMC should
bump into another place which at least  SSC
MTS Admit Card released, send it at the first price.
I find it attractive.
If you want to wait a little more between the 2768 parts, then you
can tweet the price of 2460 and a half acquaintances, due to which the company for which is very
good for potential in the future. The
last company of our discussion today is
Maruti Suzuki India Limited. I do
not need to tell you much about it. It is
a market leader in the four-wheeler auto sector. It has
more than fifty percent of the
market. More than half of the vehicles
you see on the road are of Maruti Suzuki. Then
you will come to know how big the hotel
company is. How much market share does
Maruti Suzuki have over the market.
So f-18 cigarette companies, the four-
wheeler auto sector, battery companies, heavy
companies are very good companies. Follow me if
you are searching for investment properties in Maruti Suzuki.
If you have long term
investment potential in it, then the
price rate is 66667 from military discharge to 6820.
Thank you. Very attractive price. Jabalpur
starting urination in Maruti Suzuki 800
toilet invested, but if a little  If you
want to wait, you can see 060, it was
supported there many times, so caffeine
means there are two constables of easy postponement,
this investment price level, if you
see long-term potential in it, then
definitely Dr to price raw test
wicketkeeper nylon, so I hope
friends, this was a quick introduction to all the digitization that we have done to
cover many staff,
but I hope
you will forgive me for that
because I gave
you a little introduction to all the staff who had the courage to discuss so many staff,
and along with that, their
decisions can be done in detail,
you can also keep all these stocks on your voice,
and along with this, there is support for enterprise travel,
you can also see notes on that,
and wherever you find nutritious, if there is
some consolidation in the market, conservation continues for a few
days, some
correction also comes, then you should keep an eye on the support of all these staff on
priceless, keep an
eye on them, and where further
changes are seen, then you can become a long-term
investor,
qualities in  Everyone can read and see it,
but you must have seen that all these entries, all such
discussions are about your used oil or in your long
term investment. Come on friends, this is today's
video, this is Knowledge Power
Supreme, this channel is commissioned to
bring the right OLX to you. In the upcoming new videos,
we will discuss many interesting offices
and I will keep bringing useful collides and topics for you.
Similarly, every record,
we will keep discussing weekly market updates and invite situations by sharing our views,
so definitely subscribe to our
channel. Event posted on Facebook. Updates. If
you like today's video content, then
like the video. If you think that this
mission can help someone, then share it
with your friends and family members
and subscribe to the channel. See
you in the next video
with the discussion of fruit coffee. Till then, take care and
new song by the channel.